A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 4
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 August 23-31 (Box 41, Folder 564)
      Speaking invitation and responses, briefing book for Niagara County.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 September (Box 42, Folder 565)
      Speaking invitation and responses, briefing book for Sullivan County.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 October 1-15 (Box 42, Folder 566)
      Speaking invitations and responses, Reading copy of Nelson A. Rockefeller speech dedicating new terminal at MacArthur Airport-10/01/66.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 October 15-31 (Box 42, Folder 567)
      Speaches, press releases, briefing book for Orleans and North Salem County.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 November (Box 42, Folder 568)
      Speaches, briefing book for Westchester County.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules (Daily), 1966 January-August (Box 43, Folder 569)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules (Daily), 1966 August-November 7 (Box 43, Folder 570)
    - Republican Party, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 571)
      Republican National Committee, biographical information (1959) and the Republican State Chairman, biographical information (1959)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1965 December (Box 43, Folder 572)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1965 December (Box 43, Folder 573)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 January 1-14 (Box 43, Folder 574)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1965 November (Box 43, Folder 575)
    - Republican State Committee, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 576)
      1960 yearbook.
    - Republican National Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 44, Folder 577)
      Officers, Executive Committee and members.
    - New York Republican State Committee, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 578)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1969 October (Box 44, Folder 579)
      Calendars September-December 1965.
    - "Regulation of Campaign Finance", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 580)
      Report by the University of California, 1955.
    - Finance Committees, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 581)
      Republican National Finance Committee, 1959-1961 and Republican State Finance Chairman, 1959.
    - State Party Lists, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 582)
      Republican State Central Committees, 1960-1965 and Republican State Chairmen, 1959-1966.
    - "Rural Citizens for Rockefeller", 1966 (Box 44, Folder 583)
      Letters from Nelson A. Rockefeller and Bernard Potter to locals, April-May 1966.
    - Cummingham, Evelyn (Assistant to Jackie Robinson), 1966 (Box 44, Folder 584)
      Correspondence, letter to Ms. Cummingham from George Bush (7/6/66), signed by Bush as candidate for Congress from Houston, Texas.
    - Insurance Committee for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 585)
      Correspondence.
    - Intergroup Relations, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 586)
      Reports.
    - State Labor Committee for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 587)
      Victor Borella, correspondence.
    - Lawyers for the Rockefeller Team, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 588)
    - Race Relations, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 589)
      Jackie Robinson correspondence and memos, politics.
    - National Negro Republican Assembly Awards Dinner Dance honoring Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 October 14 (Box 45, Folder 590)
    - Polish Committee, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 591)
      Report (undated and unsigned), circa September-October 1966.
    - Rural Citizens for the Rockefeller Team - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 592)
    - Rural Citizens for the Rockefeller Team - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 593)
      Correspondence, memos.
    - Race Relations, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 594)
      Samuel Singletary, Special Assistant to Jackie Robinson, files, correspondence, memos.
    - Sports Committee, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 595)
      Nelson A. Rockefeller Citation from Touchdown Club ("Empire State Medal for Excellence in Sports").
    - Taxpayer Campaign Material, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 596)
      Campaign incidents letter from Glaser & Glaser.
    - Veterans Committee for Rockefeller - Wilson Team, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 597)
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 598)
      1) Aging2) Agriculture3) History and Art.
    - Arts and Entertainment Committee for Governor Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 599)
      Correspondence, fund raising, master mailing list.
    - Associates of the Rockefeller Team Committee - Jewish, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 600)
      Correspondence, reports.
    - Builders for the Rockefeller Team and Republican Legislature, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 601)
    - Press Clippings, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 602)
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 603)
      1) Children, youth and family affairs2) Civil defense.
    - Columbian League, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 604)
      Press releases supporting Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 605)
      1) Conservation and outdoor recreation2) Crime, correction and criminal justice3) Economy of the state.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 606)
      1) Education (including state aid to libraries)2) Health and medical care3) Higher education.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 607)
      1) Highway safety2) Highways and the thruway3) Housing and urban renewal.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 608)
      1) Labor and social insurance2) Local government3) Mentally ill and mentally retarded.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 609)
      New York City and New York City supplement.
    - Office of Legilative Research, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 610)
      Memoranda re: highways and legilation reapportionment, memo "For the Record" re O'Connor.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 611)
      1) Public employees2) Public welfare.
    - Fact Books, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 612)
      1) Transportation2) Veterans3) Water resources - including the Pure Waters Program.
    - Transcripts of New Conferences - Q A Sessions - Radio and TV Interviews, 1966 October 28-November (Box 47, Folder 613)
    - Transcripts, 1966 October 10-26 (Box 47, Folder 614)
    - Transcripts, 1966 September 8-October 7 (Box 47, Folder 615)
    - Area Directors Thank you letters from Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 616)
    - Arts and Entertainment Committee, 1966 November 2 (Box 47, Folder 617)
      Vote and "thank you" letters from Nelson Rockefeller.
    - Baptist Ministers Thank you letters, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 618)
    - "Builders for the Rockefeller Team" Thank you letters, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 619)
    - Campaign Notes, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 620)
      Nelson Rockefeller handwritten notes re: announcement of candidacy, minutes of campaign meetings.
    - Citizens for Rockefeller Team - "Thank you" notes by Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 621)
    - Constitutional Convention - Public Employees Legal Memo, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 622)
    - Constitutional Convention - New York Rep0ublican State Committee Press Releases, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 623)
    - Constitutional Convention - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 624)
      Proposal delegates to convention, propositions for ballot.
    - Constitutional Convention - Senate Voting Results in 1965, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 625)
    - Constitutional Convention - Selection of Delegates, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 626)
      Background memos.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 627)
      Appointment of members, news articles.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing Transcript, 1966 October 3 (Box 48, Folder 628)
      pp. 1-248.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 4 (Box 48, Folder 629)
      Part I, pp. 249-397.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 4 (Box 48, Folder 630)
      Part II, pp. 398 - 556A (index to speakers).
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 10 (Box 49, Folder 631)
      Part I, pp. 557-690.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 10 (Box 49, Folder 632)
      Part II, pp. 691-846.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission - Public Hearing, 1966 October 10 (Box 49, Folder 633)
      Part III, pp. 847-933 (index).
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 11 (Box 49, Folder 634)
      Part I, pp. 934-1124.
    - Constitutional Convention - Temporary State Commission on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution - Public Hearing, 1966 October 11 (Box 49, Folder 635)
      Part II, pp. 1125 to end (index).
    - Constitutional Convention - Proposed Delegates, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 636)
    - Constitutional Convention - Background, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 637)
    - Young Republican Convention, 1966 September 7-8 (Box 49, Folder 638)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 639)
      Correspondence, paper ballots for delegate selection.
    - Constitutional Convention - Reapportionment, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 640)
    - Campaign Strategy Memos, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 641)
      John Deardourff to William Pfeiffer, Deardourff to William J. Ronan and Deardourff to John A. Wells.
    - Constitutional Convention - Delegates-at-Large Suggestions, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 642)
    - Statewide Primary for Statewide Officers, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 643)
      Memos, news articles, veto message.
    - Young Republicans - Campaign Material, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 644)
    - Constitutional Convention - Issues - Analysis of 1965 Election, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 645)
    - Constitutional Convention - Judicial Selection Memos, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 646)
    - Constitutional Convention - Law Enforcement and Crime Issues, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 647)
    - Constitutional Convention - Position Paper - Bicameral versus Unicameral Legislature for the State of New York, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 648)
    - Constitutional Convention - Background Materials, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 649)
    - Constitutional Convention - Paul Carvan Strategy Memos, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 650)
    - Young Republican Memos and Publicity, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 651)
    - Constitutional Convention - John P. Lorenzo Speech to Republican State Convention, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 652)
    - Republican Platform Committee, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 653)
      Memos re: members of Committee, public hearing schedule.
    - Republican State Campaign for the Election of Constitutional Convention Delegates - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 654)
    - Young Republicans - Progress Reports, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 655)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 656)
      Summary of proposals to amend the constitution, 1950-1966; votes on proposel amendments to constitution, 1938-1965.
    - Young Republicans - Rocky for Governor College Clubs, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 657)
    - Young Republicans - Governor's Campaign Schedules, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 658)
    - Young Republicans - Senate Campaign, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 659)
    - Young Republicans - Spanish Voters, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 660)
    - Young Republicans - Special Interest Groups, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 661)
    - Young Republicans - Voter Registration - Counties, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 662)
    - Young Republicans - Campaign Seminar - Syracuse, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 663)
    - Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 664)
      Campaign literature, meetings, conferences.
    - Housewives for the Rockefeller Team Committee, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 665)
      Literature, programs, expenses.
    - Young New Yorkers for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 666)
      Campaign activities reports.
    - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 667)
      Congratulatory notes and telegrams after re-election.
    - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 668)
      Letters of congratulations.
    - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 669)
      Letters, congratulation notes, and telegrams to victorious state and national Republican winners.
    - Rockefeller, Nelson - Campaign Contributors - Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 670)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson - Campaign Contributors - Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 671)
      Lists of substantial contributors.
    - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 672)
      Responses to victory congratulations and thank-you letters to Republican women.
    - Endorsements and Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 673)
      Individuals, organizations and newspaper editorials.
    - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 674)
      Letters to engineers and architects.
    - Field Organizations Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 675)
    - Finance Committee Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 676)
    - "Flying Squad" Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 677)
    - George Hinman - NAR Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 678)
    - Housewives Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 679)
    - Insurance Committee Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 680)
    - Labor Unions and Committees Endorsements and Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 681)
    - Labor Unions and Committees Endorsements and Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 682)
    - Lawyers Committee Pre- and Post-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 683)
    - Radio and TV Editorials and Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 684)
    - Rural Citizens Pre-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 685)
    - Special Committees Pre- and Post-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 686)
    - Sports Committee Pre-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 687)
    - Pre-Election Thank-You Letters - General, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 688)
    - Pre-Election Thank-You Letters - General, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 689)
    - Pre- and Post-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 690)
    - Pre- and Post-Election Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 691)
    - Veterans Committee for Rockefeller/Wilson Team Thank-You Letters, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 692)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (A), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 693)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (B), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 694)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (C), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 695)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (D), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 696)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (E), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 697)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (F), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 698)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (G), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 699)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (H), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 700)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (I), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 701)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (J), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 702)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (K), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 703)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (L), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 704)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (M), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 705)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (N-O), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 706)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (P-Q), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 707)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (R), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 708)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (S), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 709)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (S), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 710)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (T-U), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 711)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (U-W), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 712)
    - Congratulatory Notes Received Post-Election (X-Z), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 713)
    - Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 714)
      Notes, editorials and criticism.
    - Political Correspondence (A), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 715)
      Notes, suggestions, and a personal letter from Maryland Govenor-Elect Spiro T. Agnew.
    - Political Correspondence (B), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 716)
      Criticism and praise.
    - Political Correspondence (C), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 717)
    - Political Correspondence (D), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 718)
    - Political Correspondence (E-F), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 719)
    - Political Correspondence (G), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 720)
    - Political Correspondence (H-J), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 721)
    - Political Correspondence (K), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 722)
    - Political Correspondence (L), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 723)
    - Political Correspondence (M), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 724)
    - Political Correspondence (N-O), 1966 (Box 59, Folder 725)
      Includes telegrams from Frank O'Conner demanding debates.
    - Political Correspondence (P-R), 1966 (Box 60, Folder 726)
      Includes personal congratulations from Ronald Reagan.
    - Political Correspondence (S), 1966 (Box 60, Folder 727)
    - Political Correspondence (T-Z), 1966 (Box 60, Folder 728)
    - Debates, 1966 October-November (Box 60, Folder 729)
      1) NAR, Frank O'Conner, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr. and Paul Adams on October 29, 1966, on WABC-TV2) NAR, Frank O'Conner, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr. and Paul Adams, ground rules negotiations re: format on November 6, 1966, on WNBC-TV.
    - Press Releases, 1966 April-June (Box 60, Folder 730)
    - Press Releases, 1966 July 1-July 9 (Box 60, Folder 731)
    - Press Releases, 1966 July 10-July 16 (Box 60, Folder 732)
    - Press Releases, 1966 July 17-July 23 (Box 60, Folder 733)
    - Press Releases, 1966 July 24-July 30 (Box 61, Folder 734)
    - Press Releases, 1966 July 31-August 6 (Box 61, Folder 735)
      Transcript of August 2, 1966, press conference announcing that Senator Javits will be the Chairman of the Republican Party Campaign.
    - Press Releases, August 7-August 13, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 736)
    - Press Releases, 1966 August 14-August 20 (Box 61, Folder 737)
    - Press Releases, 1966 August 21-August 27 (Box 61, Folder 738)
    - Press Releases, 1966 August 28-September 3 (Box 61, Folder 739)
    - Press Releases, 1966 September 4-10 (Box 61, Folder 740)
    - Press Releases, 1966 September 11-17 (Box 61, Folder 741)
    - Press Releases, 1966 September 18-24 (Box 62, Folder 742)
    - Press Releases, 1966 September 25-27 (Box 62, Folder 743)
    - Press Releases, 1966 September 28-October 1 (Box 62, Folder 744)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 2-6 (Box 62, Folder 745)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 7-8 (Box 62, Folder 746)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 9-12 (Box 62, Folder 747)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 13-15; 1966 (Box 63, Folder 748)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 16-18 (Box 63, Folder 749)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 19-22 (Box 63, Folder 750)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 23-26 (Box 63, Folder 751)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 27-29 (Box 63, Folder 752)
    - Press Releases, 1966 October 30-November 2 (Box 63, Folder 753)
    - Press Releases, 1966 November 2-5 (Box 63, Folder 754)
    - Press Releases, 1966 November 6-8 (Box 63, Folder 755)
    - Adams, Paul, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 756)
      Press clippings.
    - AFL - CIO, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 757)
      Press clippings, platform proposals.
    - Aging, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 758)
    - Alcoholism, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 759)
    - Aldrish, Alexander - Cousin, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 760)
      Split over Medicaid.
    - Almeida, Salvatore, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 761)
      Democratic Assemblyman.
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 762)
      Press release re: liberals.
    - Anti-Poverty and Job Development, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 763)
    - Applaacian Thruway - Map, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 764)
    - Aruleo, Angel J., 1966 (Box 64, Folder 765)
      Appointment via chair of New York City Rockefeller campaign.
    - Arts, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 766)
      Olana historic site, Saratoga Arts Center, press releases.
    - Bay Ridge, Brooklyn, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 767)
    - Bayside, Queens, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 768)
    - Special Committee - "Independent Voters for Rockefeller and Lefkowitz", 1966 (Box 64, Folder 769)
      Filing, news clippings.
    - "Friends of the Rockefeller Team" Radio Company, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 770)
      TV and radio stations.
    - Laverne, Thomas - New York State Senator - WCBS-TV - "Legisislative Hearing", 1966 (Box 64, Folder 771)
    - Levitt, Arthur - Letter to Weekly Press (Callan), 1966 (Box 64, Folder 772)
    - Lindsay, John V. - Transcript - WCBS-TV - Newsmakers, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 773)
    - McGuire, Eugene Associates, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 774)
      Democratic endorsement of Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - Nakasin, Samuel, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 775)
      Photograph. Press release-speaker's bureau.
    - Nickerson, Eugene - Transcript - WCBS-TV - Newsmaker, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 776)
    - Nickerson, Eugene - Keynote Address - Democratic State Convention, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 777)
    - O'Connor, Frank, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 778)
      Biographical material, acceptance speed at Democratic Convention, Civic Pollution Program, press clippings.
    - O'Connor, Frank, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 779)
      Challenge Nelson A. Rockefeller to debate, news clippings, position papers-Condon-Wadlin repeal, conservation.
    - Rockefeller Campaign Team Materials, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 780)
      Information Committee for the Rockefeller Team, Friends of the Rockefeller Team, Citizens for the Rockefeller Team leases, bank information, agreements for political broadcasts.
    - Cocktail Party at 21 Club, 1966 October 21 (Box 64, Folder 781)
      Invitation lists, prospect lists, mailing list.
    - Committee Lists - Volunteer Cards, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 782)
    - Consents - To Use of Name by Citizens Committee for Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 783)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 784)
      Portions of files of Alexander Halpern, Citizens Committee Chairman, acknowledgements of contribution.
    - Daily Contributions, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 785)
      Memos, lists, copies of checks.
    - Financial Reports - Citizen's Committee - Filings with Secretary of State, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 786)
    - Financial Reports - Information Committee - Filings, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 787)
    - Insurance Policies - Citizens Committee, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 788)
    - Information Committee - Legal, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 789)
    - Contributors - Master Lists, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 790)
    - Prospective Members of Citizens Committee for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 791)
    - Citizens Committee for the Rockefeller Team - Organization, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 792)
    - Citizens Committee - Campaign Contributions Receipts, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 793)
    - Citizens Committee - Reports, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 794)
      Final report, reports from other committees, misc.
    - Advertising - Tinker and Partners, Inc. - Volume I - Campaign Book, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 795)
    - Advertising - Tinker and Partners, Inc. - Volume II - Campaign Book, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 796)
    - Advertising, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 797)
      Report on effectiveness of two TV commericials - "Fish" and "Taxes," media strategy proposal.
    - Aldrick, Alexander ("SAM"), 1966 (Box 66, Folder 798)